Aah!
Hey, good night, Sammy.
G'night, Normulon.
Mm.
Ahh!
I'm sorry, sir, but
we're about to close.
Oh, I won't be long... Sammy.
Scarab: This might be
the most delicious tea
I've ever tasted.
I almost understand why
you abandoned your post
for this quaint life...
Kheirosiphon.
No.
You!
I'm not going back!
I don't like sacred flames.
I like tea!
Aaaaahhhh!
Who's next?
Hmm.
No.
Huh.
Finally.
Wyatt:
Aren't you gonna answer that?
Ah...
Mr. P-Prismo...
Just ignore it.
Make your wish.
Well, I'm trying to, but...
it's kinda... distracting.
You have no idea what it took.
The terrible things I
did just to get here.
And now I can't
even concentrate!
The wish... Spit it out.
Oh. Ughh. Aagh!
Oh, I wish it
was quiet enough to think!
Wish granted.
Oh, wait. Uh...
Okay, fine.
A crossover. Okay.
Oh, hey! Ooo.
Hmm...
That's not a crossover.
Nope.
Oh, my gosh, you really
are Fionna and Cake!
The real ones!
Oh, crud!
Can we go on an adventure?
Heh, well...
Aw, my hat!
Ayo! What's going
on now, Cake?
I don't know,
but this is cool.
Ugh! What's wrong
with Cake's voice?
Whoa! Big boy!
No, this is gonna drive me nuts.
Hey!
Heeeeeeeeeeeeey!
Hmm. She's off-model, too.
Whoa! I'm standing
on my back legs!
Oh! Arms!
Legs are arms!
Amazing!
It's like a video game,
and we're getting upgrades
for beating those weirdos.
Ha! I can stretch!
He-eeey. Ha ha!
Much better.
Do me next!
Aw! I just wanted cool powers.
Maybe you have some.
Try flying.
Ha ha! Faster! Faster!
These two are a
long way from home.
But how?
Maybe the connection
is open again.
Nope. Still locked out.
Then how did they get here?
I stepped through a portal
in that sad man's head.
Better take a closer look.
Now what?
For starters, let's
get you covered.
Great.
What happened with this
one and this one, Simon?
I didn't do anything.
Liar. Crossovers
don't just happen!
Look, it seems like you two
have some stuff to work out,
so can you send us back to Ooo?
Shh.
Let's try rewinding.
What the heck, dude?
Well, you couldn't
bring her back,
so I helped myself.
Who's her?
I've got limits
to my power, bro.
That doesn't give you an
excuse to mess with my stuff.
Whatever, dude.
Simon, I mean it.
Just because it's in your
head doesn't mean it's yours.
Ooooh, I've always wanted
to try one of these.
Drink the
water, you beast!
You...
You beast of burden,
drink the water.
Drink. Drink this water!
Hey! That's not a toy!
Bad cat!
Aah! Why would you do that?!
Nobody sprays Cake!
Hyah!
Who do you think you
are, you big bully?
And why'd you bring us here?
Where is here?!
Okay, o-kay.
Chill.
Wow, okay.
I am Prismo the Wishmaster.
That tells me nothing!
Well, as Wishmaster, I grant...
wishes.
And sometimes those wishes
require me to create
new wish-altered realities.
Here, check it out.
A wish made this
"farmworld" universe.
funny shape universe.
This one already existed.
I don't even remember
whose wish this was.
Oh!
This universe is special
because it had my favorite guy.
Roooar! Pancake!
There he is! Heh heh heh.
Dog person.
Lotsa wishes, lotsa worlds.
The Time Room is the perch
from which I keep my eye
on the resulting multiverse.
Okay. Keep going.
Uh, I used to
really like my job.
But after eons of
making stuff for others,
I wondered what it would be like
to make something for myself.
Let's see.
She's gonna be a good fighter,
so she'll need a badass sword.
Annnnd... everyone
needs a best friend.
Ooh, cats are cool.
And now just to put them
in a big ol' tree house
on a grassy field
in a magical world.
Done.
Huh...
Shoot. Did I just
copy Finn and Jake?
Meh.
So I just leaned into it.
Maybe it wasn't the most
creative thing I could make,
but I liked writing
your stories.
Wait! That's us!
Yeah, totally.
You had adventure.
You had romance.
DJ Flame!
You had friends.
Gum-Garry.
Marshall's a vampire.
Wow, we look so happy.
I knew my life was
supposed to be magic.
Fionna and Cake was
real this whole time?
Pretty tight, right?
Yeah. So why'd you change it?
Yeah, our world doesn't
look like that at all.
Everything's boring as hell.
Hmm.
Oh, I think I know
what happened.
No wonder you guys
looked so terrible
when you first got here.
Okay, so, technically,
I'm not supposed to
make stuff for myself.
So I kinda had to
"hide" your universe.
I found the emptiest,
most cursed magical brain
in all of Ooo.
Fionna: Him?
Kinda.
Ice King!
Huh?
Hey, Ice King, can I store a
fan-made alternate universe
in your cursed dome?
Sure, magic flashlight!
You can put anything
you want in there.
'Specially if it's
got a hot lady.
Cool. Hold still for upload.
Whoa! Fire in the hole!
Fionna and Cake:
What time is it?
You were like a big
nutty hard drive.
And everything went great...
until you got cured.
Simon! Your crown!
What's happenin', lady?
Don't panic, but I think
GOLB is digesting us...
breaking us apart
layer by layer...
down to our essential forms.
Betty?
It's good to see you, Simon.
It's good to be seen.
Dang. From fun
wizard to sad loser.
He wasn't fun. He was insane.
I dunno. He looked
pretty happy to me.
Prismo: Without the
curse of the magic crown,
Simon's brain was
no longer magical.
So your world must have
lost its magic, too.
And I've been locked
out ever since.
Oh, Betty.
So, all of this is really bad,
but I think we're gonna be okay.
As long as no one else knows.
Oh, no!
Quick, down the stairs!
What stairs?
Oh! Shoot.
I'll deal with whoever that is.
You guys follow me to the exit.
Up, up, up.
Just a minute!
Scarab! Hey!
Curious.
I always thought you
had an open door policy.
Everybody's pal, Prismo.
Hey! That's me!
Well, What brings
you here Scrabby?
No one
calls me that anymore.
I was passing through
the neighborhood,
making a delivery to
the Judgement Hall,
when I got an alert...
about you.
Me?
Your Universe Breach
Alarm went off twice
and went ignored?
Oh. I just needed to
change the batteries.
Nothing for an important
guy like you to worry about.
Yeah, everything in the
Time Room is going great.
Yeah, well, thanks
for coming by.
I know you're really busy, so...
Prismo, it almost seems
like you're trying
to get rid of me...
What? No, no!
I love it when you stop by.
Let's bro out! We can
party like we used to.
I was never invited to parties.
Well, time to fix that.
Ugh. We just want
to go back to Ooo.
Why are we hiding?
Remember when I said
I wasn't supposed
to create new
realities for myself?
It's actually a big deal
and I could get in
serious trouble for it.
The guy who was at the
door, that's the Scarab.
He's a jerk god-auditor.
And if he finds out about
you, he's gonna report me.
And then... gugh...
My boss is gonna
drop the hammer!
Your boss?
Gah! Simon!
- Whoa!
- Fionna!
- Oof!
- Ugh!
Ugh. Ow! Whoa!
It's okay, Fionna, walking
on two legs is hard.
It's not my legs,
it's this damn skirt.
Girl, you look good though.
Weird. You never
had any trouble
with skirts in my stories.
Ah!
How about shorts, huh?
What? What do you
mean "shorts"?
Uh, you know, mortals.
I call them "shorts" because
they're smaller than us.
And their lives
are really short.
Having
two conversations
at the same time is hard.
Oh! That's mine.
Is this cat hair yours, too?
I don't recall...
I'd like to take a
look around the cube
and see if there are any more...
"batteries" that need changing.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Uh-oh. We'll take a
shortcut through the core.
Pick up the pace, Simon!
You really don't want to
get caught by this guy!
I don't care.
I mean, you show me
all my messed-up past
and expect me to just shrug
it off like it's no big deal.
"Just move forward, Simon."
Well, maybe I don't
want to move forward.
Maybe I just want
to sit right here.
Ugh, this guy.
Oh, sweet!
Wow!
What the heck are those things?
That's the Time Core.
I don't think they're
actually alive.
Maybe? They send time waves
throughout the multiverse
that are experienced
as the passage of time.
Now, see, you said
that word before,
and I pretended to understand,
but I've got the
education of a house cat.
What's the multi-universe?
I'll show you.
This is the multiverse,
a huge web of all the
different realities
elegantly connected
like an anthill
or a camp counselor
relationship chart.
Where is our world on this map?
Your universe is...
unauthorized, so, it's...
waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaay
over here.
Dang, that looks so lonely.
Yeah, because I kind of made
your universe off the books,
it can't really be
part of the multiverse.
Just the fact that
you exist could have
totally unpredictable effects
on the other realities.
You're like free radicals.
Awesome! That sounds cool!
Yeah...
So majestic.
Trillions of waves of time
spreading across creation
in a mighty gush.
Eh, the colors
give me a headache.
Prismo!
Are we close?
Just through this door.
Finally! We're going
back adventurin'!
I can't wait!
Huh? Huh?
Is the circle ready?
Just finished.
Oh, hey, what's up?
And the new battery?
You already know.
You're me. Ha-ha.
Yeah, this is confusing.
Prismo! Where's the exit?!
It's been cool hanging out...
but you got to go back now.
- What!?
Together: Simon... do the
thing with the portal!
No way.
I am not going through
that heartache again.
We're out, too!
- Stop!
- We go where we want!
Fionna! Cake!
That's the last time I make
an unauthorized universe.
Unauthorized universe?
Crap.
What do you think about
the stuff he said?
Are we not real people?
Heck
yeah, we're real!
So what if he made us?
We're making our own
selves from now on!
I always knew you
were a smart cat.
Ugh!
Ah, come on, Scrabby.
Let's make a deal. I can
get you anything you want!
A new ride? Big dung ball?
Ah! Not my hot n' spicy.
You just handed me
the only thing I want.
My pickles? The Time Room!
I should have been Wishmaster,
and I will be!
All I have to do is turn
in your rogue universe
to prove you're unworthy.
Pssh, what am I worried
about? You'll never find him.
It's hidden in a person?
Crap, crap!
He's here, isn't he?
No.
I donked up.
Join the club.
We've been running for so
long, I'm gonna throw up.
There's a light up ahead.
It must be the exit!
Hold on!
- Adventure time!
- Huh?
What's up?
What the heck?
Did you just make us go
through a big circle?
Okay,
we're out of time.
You need to get back
inside his head now.
Found you!
Ah, the crossovers.
You're evidence.
You're getting egged, too.
And after that,
into the incinerator with
the rest of the trash.
Uh... no!
They're Fionna and Cake...
and they go where they want!
Run!
And keep running!
This dude will hunt
you like a polar bear!
Prismo...
Hit the button and hold
on tight to each other!
What's the point?
Ow! You dum-dum!
If you don't help us,
Simon, our entire world
and everyone we know will die!
Please! Help us!
Go!
Actually, I think I
might be able to...
Are we back in the magic world?
No, this doesn't look like Ooo.
What are we gonna do?
That bug guy's still after
us and we can't take him on.
I used to be able to stop whole
armies of jerks like that,
but I'm useless now.
Uh, yeah, we know.
Ooh! Maybe this
can get us back.
Yeah!
Hmm... Hmm...
Let's just button mash it.
Wait, wait, wait!
We don't know
what channel number
corresponds to Ooo.
We could end right
back in the Time Room
where the Scarab will
bite my head off!
Well, I could use a bite.
I'm hungry, Fionna.
I'll check my new backpack.
Got anything in
that big ol' muumuu?
Oh, found something.
Sandwiches!
I know a way I can protect
you from the Scarab,
bring back magic to your world,
and make it last forever.
I need to become Ice King again.